

RAZVAN ZAMFIR

Web Developer

CONTACT

+43 676 7048104

Hermagor 9620, Austria

🔀 razvan.zamfir.986@gmail.com

in LinkedIn Profile

Personal Website

EDUCATION

CARINTHIA UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES

Bachelor of Arts in Intercultural Business Management: Graduated with distinction

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

- → WordPress
- → HTML, XML
- → CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS
- → JavaScript, React.js, jQuery, Vite.js
- → PHP, MySQL
- → Object-oriented programming

LANGUAGES

German - Conversational (B2) English - Business fluent (C2) Romanian - Native

ABOUT ME

I am a solution-oriented individual with a love for diversity, new knowledge, and practical applications of technology. I work well both alone and in teams while maintaining a high level of autonomy and professionalism. I'm experienced in web development, digital marketing and project management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

WORDPRESS MANAGER & WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance (Mar 2023 - Present)

• Developed a variety of small and medium-sized applications and websites requiring a multitude of programming languages and libraries, as well as development and visual editing tools.

GAS STATION CASHIER & CLERK

OMV (Apr 2022 - Dec 2022)

- Managed the cash register and several subsystems (Lotto, mobile services handler, washing station).
- Monitored and ensured the proper functionality of machinery and devices designated for gas stations.
- Acted as the main liaison for troubleshooting and solving technical issues.
- Provided best-in-class customer service.

IT LEAD (VOLUNTEER)

SIETAR Austria (Nov 2021 - Apr 2022)

- Administered the institution's WordPress platform, ensuring its proper functioning.
- Lead the redesigning process for the institution's website.
- Added new features to the website (various plugins & design elements).
- Maintained strategic communication with the European branch.
- Provided technical assistance to the President in various organizational projects.



RAZVAN ZAMFIR

Web Developer

OTHER SKILLS

- → Adobe Photoshop
- → Canva
- → MS Office Suite
- → Google Suite
- → Digital Marketing
- → Search Engine Optimisation
- → Project Management
- → Highly adaptable

WORK EXPERIENCE

PLATFORM MANAGER & MARKETING SPECIALIST

Comfort & Views Austria (Mar 2021 - Nov 2021)

- Managed the business website, Booking, Airbnb, and social media platforms.
- Managed reservation changes, cancellations, and released updates.
- Answered guest communications and reservation inquiries via email and phone.
- Ensured a remarkable customer experience & top property rating.

STUDENT INTERN

Flex (Mar 2021 - May 2021)

- Created and distributed an employee opinion survey across the company's engineering department.
- Performed national and international market research in the EMS industry with relation to the company.
- Developed a business report comprising the survey analysis and the market research findings, as well as a future prospect and suggested actions for the company.